today we will talk about the success criterion
3.1.4 abbreviations of the guidelines
for the accessibility of the W3C
first of all what is the purpose of this criterion
the purpose of this criterion is to
ensure that users can
access the extended form of abbreviations
or have a meaning of a
word that could have various
meanings on the page are created in this way
two situations the situation a and la
quote b situation a when the
abbreviation has only one meaning
within the page to the situation
b when the abbreviation can have several
meanings always within the
same page later we can
we can provide explanation
for the first occurrence of the abbreviation
or for all occurrences of
abbreviations on a page in the situation
in b instead we can provide
expansion an explanation for all
occurrences of abbreviations on a page
web
so we have various techniques that have us
helped to solve this criterion
one of these is g 55 or il
link to definitions in this
technique
we thus create a link with the
word to a site, an external source, that
explains it, in this case, this is the
line of code in this case I put
the acronym afp I gave it the name
alphafetoprotein and the element a I put on it
the source of the site by going to the page
html we can see example g55 afp
the page exits with the explanation of
this acronym subsequently we pass
to the h28 technique or that of
provide definitions using
an element called abbr this
element requires us the title, in fact
for example I have put to the element
abbr
the text "Ex."
I have put it with the title example
, i.e. the extended form of the initials e
also because for www or world wilde web
the result is so the user is enough
which places the cursor
above the page with the abbr element and
a mini view with the content comes out
which gives us the extended form of the
abbreviation. then there is the g70 technique
that is, provide a function to search
an online dictionary using
simply the i link element
the word dictionary putting
the source of an external online dictionary
in this case the braid one where one
could search for any word and
he gets the definition later
there is the h 60 technique or the use
of a link element for linking
to an always external glossary in this
case we linked the "grossario.html" e
with
the element a we linked the page
glossary.html I created
externally, or now I show,
or this by clicking on
on the link ie if the glossary ball
that I created externally by doing
unlisted lists and I made a mini
glossary putting in two words at random
, then we pass to the technique which is the
G97 which
provides a first use of
abbreviations and
immediately there after provides an extended form of
an acronym in this case simply
after the acronym W3C I put between
parenthesis the extended form by writing
world wide web consortium
finally we come to the last technique is
the G62 or supply is always a
glossary in this case we use a
element a to link to the glossary that
this time it is inside the page
so to do this we put the ID
glossary to the ul element for the
list that was the glossary I have
copied, which was also on the page
glossary.html e
then as the link of the word glossary
I put the hashtag to link the ID and
maybe adding up you can
see that when one goes to click glossary there
leads directly to the glossary that will be
scattered across the page
web where one can go to find ea
see the definition of the word thus
[Music]
thanks to the realization of these 6
techniques we are
managed to meet the criterion of
success of abbreviations
all this however was
documented in this document with
lines of code and explanations
goodbye prof